* [My Account](javascript:WebForm_DoPostBackWithOptions(new WebForm_PostBackOptions("ctl00$lb_account", "", false, "", "../account/", false, true)))
*  [Login](javascript:__doPostBack('ctl00$lb_logoutx',''))

#### Privacy Policy

YourOpinion recognises the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about our members of the YourOpinion site. This privacy policy should be read in conjunction with the terms and conditions of the website.

The personal information collected is used solely for the purpose of conducting market research and surveys. Only relevant information necessary to fulfill the research objectives will be processed and we only collect personal information from you when you communicate with us by any media. This includes (but is not limited to) registration on the site, completing a survey, sending us an email, participating in polls and online discussions on YourOpinion and participating in online market research communities. The information we collect about you includes information about your views in respect of the subject matter of our surveys together with demographic information. This may include sensitive information within the meaning of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) such as:

* your racial or ethnic origin;
* your political opinions or membership of a political association;
* your religious or philosophical beliefs or affiliations;
* your physical or mental health or condition;
* your sexual life;
* your criminal history, including any offences you have committed or are alleged to have committed and any proceedings that you have faced in respect of that;
* your membership of any trade unions or professional or trade associations.

Sensitive information will only be collected with your consent and only if it's directly related to, or reasonably necessary for, the research we conduct or used to target surveys to you.

Please be advised that your phone calls and emails to YourOpinion may be recorded and monitored for quality control purposes. We may also intercept communications made to individual members of staff of YourOpinion when this is required for business purposes.

For further details on how YourOpinion processes your personal information, your rights in relation to your personal information and how to contact us, please refer to our full [Privacy Policy](https://www.accenture.com/au-en/about/privacy-policy)

Sign Up

#### Prize Draw

The YourOpinion Quarterly Prize Draw gives you a chance to win $1,000 and other prizes. Simply enter by participating in our quick polls, surveys and forums.  

#### Contact Us

* **Address:** YourOpinion, 3 Sussex Street, Sydney, NSW 2000
    
* **Email:** [\[email protected\]](https://www.youropinion.com.au/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

© FiftyFive5, part of Accenture Song 2018. All Rights Reserved.
